let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1.,
        question: ' "Google" is one of the most popular ___',
        answer: 'C. Search Engine ',
        options: [
            'A. Portal',
            'B. Browser',
            'C. Search Engine',
            'D. None of these'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2.,
        question: 'E-commerce technologies have improvedupon trditional commerce technologies in ____',
        answer: 'C. Both richness and reach',
        options: [
            'A. Richness',
            'B. Reach',
            'C. Both richness and reach',
            'D. Neither richness and reach'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3.,
        question: 'The purpose of supply chain management is :',
        answer: 'C. Integrating Supply and Demand',
        options: [
            'A. Provide Customer',
            'B. Improve Quality of a Product',
            'C. Integrating Supply and Demand',
            'D. Increase Production'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4.,
        question: 'A problem statement must be',
        answer: 'A. Clear and concise description of the issue',
        options: [
            'A. Clear and concise description of the issue',
            'B. Infeasible to everyone',
            'C. Lenghty',
            'D. All of the above'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5.,
        question: 'Which among of the following is an example of E-commerce',
        answer: 'C. E-trade.com',
        options: [
            'A. Amazon.com',
            'B. Baazar.com',
            'C. E-trade.com',
            'D. None of these'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6.,
        question: 'Which one of the following is not a principle of ecommerce ?',
        answer: 'D. None of these',
        options: [
            'A. privacy',
            'B. integrity',
            'C. authentication',
            'D. None of these'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7.,
        question: 'Unique value auction is mainly applies to ?',
        answer: 'B. Second hand products',
        options: [
            'A. New products',
            'B. Second hand products',
            'C. Engineering products',
            'D. None of the above'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8.,
        question: 'The solution for all bussiness need is',
        answer: 'B. ERP',
        options: [
            'A. EDI',
            'B. ERP',
            'C. SCM',
            'D. None of the above'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9.,
        question: 'Which type of product is lesser purchased using e commerce',
        answer: 'D. none',
        options: [
            'A. automobiles',
            'B. books ',
            'C. software',
            'D. none'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10.,
        question: 'Which of the following statements accurately reflect the impact technology',
        answer: 'D. all of the above',
        options: [
            'A. Technology has caused buyer power to increase',
            'B. Technology has lessened the entry barriers for man',
            'C. Technology has increased the threat of substitute produs: and services',
            'D. all of the above'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11.,
        question: '___ allows the person to type ion just the main word words and the site will come in',
        answer: 'C. domain',
        options: [
            'A. web page',
            'B. home page',
            'C. domain',
            'D. none of these'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12.,
        question: ' Which of the following is not a limitation of the current Internet',
        answer: 'C. insufficient reach',
        options: [
            'A. Insufficient capacity throughout the backbone',
            'B. network architecture limitations',
            'C. insufficient reach',
            'D. best-efforts qos'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13.,
        question: "The component of TCP/IP that provides the Internet's addressing scheme and is responsible for the actual delivery of packets is",
        answer: 'B. ip',
        options: [
            'A. tcp',
            'B. ip',
            'C. the network layer',
            'D. the application layer'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14.,
        question: 'ESN stands for___',
        answer: 'C. Entrepreneur Social Networks',
        options: [
            'A. Enterprise Special Networks',
            'B. Enterprise Social Networks',
            'C. Entrepreneur Social Networks',
            'D. Essential Social Networks'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15.,
        question: 'Collaboration 2.0 is also known as____',
        answer: 'B. Social Collaboration',
        options: [
            'A. Social Enterprise',
            'B. Social Collaboration',
            'C. Collaboration Commerce',
            'D. Collaboration Media'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16.,
        question: 'Social networking is____',
        answer: 'B. Individual-centric',
        options: [
            'A. Group-centric',
            'B. Individual-centric',
            'C. Organization-centric',
            'D. Society-centric'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17.,
        question: 'Which of the following can a virus do?',
        answer: 'D. None of the above',
        options: [
            'A. Hurt your hardware',
            "B. Hurt any files they weren't designed to attack",
            'C. Infect files on write-protected disks',
            'D. None of the above'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18.,
        question: 'The World Wide Web (WWW) was year __',
        answer: 'A. 1994',
        options: [
            'A. 1994',
            'B. 1996',
            'C. 1992',
            'D. 1990'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19.,
        question: 'Digital Cash has following characteristic:',
        answer: 'D. All of above',
        options: [
            'A. (1) Anonymity',
            'B. Security',
            'C. Confidentiality',
            'D. All of above'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20.,
        question: 'Which among the following is not an user of B2C e-commerce?',
        answer: 'D. none',
        options: [
            'B. distributors',
            'C. Publishers',
            'D. none'
        ]
    }

]